xoriant.com 2007-08-10

# Xoriant Solutions

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
Copyright © 2005 Xoriant, Inc. All Rights Reserved.

Xoriant respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. You can view our web site without divulging any personal information about yourself, however certain content on our web site requires registration and the transmittal of personal information. We have created this Privacy Statement to disclose what happens with the personal information you provide to us through this process. At any time, you have the ability to visit the subscription center and deactivate any access you registered for or terminate receipt of communications from us.

There are times when it is important for us to request information from you. Such requests may be part of registration, feedback, online surveys, contests, and/or order forms. Some of our forms request users to provide personal information that is required for us to process the user's request. Occasionally, other information is also requested from the user to determine the demographics of Xoriant's audience. For example, we might ask for Name, Company Name, Address, E-mail Address.

At no time, however, will Xoriant, sell, trade, rent or distribute personal information to any outside organization.

This web site may make message boards, forums, chat rooms, and/or news groups available to its users. Please understand that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. These areas shall be used in a noncommercial manner only. You shall not publish or otherwise distribute any content containing a solicitation of funds, advertising, promotion, solicitation for goods or services, or other commercial matter. Except where expressly authorized by Xoriant, you agree not to store or collect data about other users on the web site.

Xoriant may provide links to Internet sites maintained by others. Xoriant is not responsible for the contents of, or any products or services offered in, those third party web sites. You should be aware when you are leaving Xoriant's web sites and be sure to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. Any links provided by Xoriant to any third party web site are provided to you as a convenience only. You should not infer that Xoriant endorses or accepts responsibility for non-Xoriant web sites by the inclusion of any such links to those web sites.
